Stephen Barraclough

26 Gilmour Street Kilmarnock

East Ayrshire, KA1 3HP **Mobile:** 07479554537

 $\textbf{Email:} \ \underline{Barraclough 0205@gmail.com}$

Website: www.barracloud.com



Personal Profile

UWS Computer networking undergraduate student studying in year 3 of my degree. I'm currently looking for part-time positions with flexibility around university commitments whilst I work towards my educational and career goals in the IT sector. With over 12 years of customer service experience and a proven history of timekeeping, teamwork, communication, computer skills, and work ethic, I can be an asset to any team.

Education and Qualifications

College: James Watt College

Subject	Level	Grade	Date
Computing & IT	NC	PASS	August 2007
Computer Games Development	NC	PASS	August 2008
Computing & IT	HNC	PASS	August 2009
Computer Networking	BSc	Level 7	May 2020
UWS Court Medal Award	BSc	Level 7	May 2020
Computer Networking	BSc	Level 8	Current

School: Ardrossan Academy

6 Standard Grades at Grades 3-5 including Maths and English

Employment History

Employer: B&M

Date: March 2021 – Current Role: Till / Floor Staff

Job Description: Fast-paced sales environment, duties include unpacking deliveries, placing products on shelves, following floor plans for product placements and stock replenishment.

Operation of the till, cash handling, tannoy systems, and general housekeeping.

Employment History

Employer: Cloudhelix / Ecko

Date: October 2021 – December 2021 **Role:** Placement / work experience

Job Description: Working with the Cloudhelix team as part of 3rd Year university project placement, gained experience within the networking environment. This included exposure to the following systems.

- Virtualization through vSphere / vCenter / vCloud
- Remote management through vmWare horizon / mRemoteNG
- Ticketing system management through Harmony / Freshdesk and slack
- Nagios system monitoring configuration and Veeam backup management

Employer: Curry / Pc World

Date: November 2019 – March 2020 **Role:** Salesperson

Job Description: Fast-paced target-based sales position helping customers have the best experience in the store to find the right products for them. Working across all areas of the store as needed to support my colleagues to deliver on store KPI's. Record sales, customer interactions, and demonstrations performed as well as provide continuous feedback to alert management of key issues in store.

Employer: Teleperformance (Clydesdale & Yorkshire bank)

Date: May 2016 - November 2019 **Role:** Customer Assistant

Job Description: Tasked with answering inbound calls, projecting a professional company image through phone interaction with new and existing clients. Main duties include answering customer inquiries, resolving their problems, up-selling & making appointments as well as processing orders, faxes, keeping customers details up to date, and recording any account notes

Customer Support Assistant – Complex & Niche – March 2018-November 2019 Working closely with colleagues in a busy team to answer complicated and unusual banking queries with a focus on Internet and Mobile banking. Involves quickly understanding new lines of business and adapting to deal with different types of inquiries. Requires communicating with other departments and corroborating different sources of information, with daily use of office suites and ICT knowledge.

Employer: Argos

Date: Oct 2010 – May 2016 **Role:** Warehouse / Team leader

Job Description: Responsible for the safety and security of staff and business during deliveries along with being responsible for ensuring my team was ready for waste uplift by the delivery crew, frequently working with customers, with experience including order fulfilment, till operation, customer service as well as product demonstration. I was also responsible for stock replenishment, rotation, including quality control standards too.

Team Leader – November 2012 – January 2013

Managing the Delivery team to ensure a fluid operation of our stockroom. Time management, quality control along with efficiency along with associated paperwork. I reverted to my previous role as a warehouse assistant as the position was temporary.

Company References	Level	Name	Contact
Cloud Helix	Manager	Grant Meek	07414643336
B&M	Manager	Darren Mciever	01563 520 290